(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
あれ？
Wait?
みんなー！見える？聞こえる？
Everyone! Can you see me? Can you hear me?
やっほー！
Yahoo!
お誕生日おめでとうありがとうね！
Thank you for the birthday wishes!
ありがとう！あっ、ありがとうございます。
Thank you! Ah, thank you very much.
え、なんか今日は、こねライブをしに来たんだけど、
Um, I came here to do a live performance today,
誕生日だからね！
Since it's my birthday!
でもなんか、運営さんに事務所に来いって言われて、
But the staff told me to come to the office,
ここに来ました。
So I came here.
あの、なぜ呼ばれたんでしょうか？
Um, why was I called here?
今、運営さんから、なんかころねクイズを用意してきたから、
Apparently, the staff prepared a "Korone Quiz" for me,
それに答えないとライブさせてくれないみたいです。
And it seems they won't let me perform unless I answer it.
なんでやねん！え、クイズを？
Why though?! Eh, a quiz?
これ、あ、あ、あー。
This... ah, ah, ah.
なるほどね、あ、じゃあこれ四択で答えていく感じね。
I see. So I have to answer these 4-choice questions.
あ、じゃあ簡単じゃん、これ。
Oh, that's easy then.
あ、光る！ちょっと見て！
Oh, it lights up! Look!
ほい、ほい、ほい、ほい、ほい、ほい！
Hoi, hoi, hoi, hoi, hoi, hoi!
あははは！あ、遊んでいって。
Ahahaha! Ah, just playing around.
なんか準備しとるっぽーい。え、これは全問正解とかあるんです？
Looks like they're preparing something. Wait, do I have to get them all correct?
あ、なんか全問正解しないとライブやっちゃダメなんだって。
Ah, apparently I'm not allowed to perform unless I get them all right.
あ、8人のメンバーからクイズを募集してきたから、
They've collected questions from 8 members,
それに全問正解しないとダメっぽい。
So it looks like I have to get every one correct.
ライブしに来たのに！
Even though I came here to perform!
え、これ、もう、準備できました？
Um, is it ready yet?
あ、よし！
Ah, alright!
じゃあ、早速行くよ。
Well then, let's get started.
あ、なんかね、ころねに関するクイズだって。しかも。
Apparently, it's a quiz about Korone. And on top of that...
って、簡単じゃんね！
Well, that's easy!
じゃあ、第一問目！
Now, for the first question!
かかってこいよ！
Bring it on!
ころねのTwitterで「場所」という項目に
What is the word Korone has written in the "Location" field
記入している言葉はなーんでしょう？
on her Twitter profile?
こんなん簡単じゃん。
This is so easy.
悪のエッグマンランド、
Evil Eggmanland,
DOOMのドッグ、
DOOM dog,
え、MOTHERオネット、ニャンピョウのフエマイスター。
MOTHER Onett, and Nyanpyo's Flute Meister.
これは...
This is...
こっちだ。
This one.
カチッ！
Click!
4の、ニャンピョウのフエマイスター！
Number 4: Nyanpyo's Flute Meister!
いぇーい！
Yay!
ありがとー！え、こんなん簡単だよ、みんな。
Thank you! See, this is easy, everyone.
簡単だよね。
It's easy, right?
正解でーす！
Correct!
フブキちゃんありがとね、
Thank you, Fubuki-chan,
ころねのためにクイズ考えてくれたんだ。
for thinking up a quiz for me.
ありがと、ありがと。
Thank you, thank you.
じゃあ、第二問目、早い、早すぎるかな？
Now for the second question. Fast, maybe too fast?
第二問目行っちゃうよ。
Going to the second question.
じゃあ、第二問いください！
Well then, second question please!
なーんだこれ？
What's this?
このサムネイルはなんの配信の時のサムネでしょうか？
Which stream is this thumbnail from?
あ、これ覚えてるよ、これ。
Oh, I remember this one.
マリリンか。
Is that Marilyn?
これはね、ころね覚えてます。
Korone remembers this one.
おかころ雑談、おかころ対戦ゲーム、おかころ歌、おかころホラーゲーム。
OkaKoro Zatsudan, Versus Game, Songs, or Horror Game.
これは、4番のおかころホラーゲームのサムネです。
This is the thumbnail for number 4: OkaKoro Horror Game.
いぇーい！
Yay!
あはははは！やい、やい、やい、やい！
Ahahaha! Yai yai yai yai!
ありがと！ありがと！
Thank you! Thank you!
これは結構覚えてて。
I remember this one quite well.
おかゆと二人で一緒に、あの...
Okayu and I, the two of us together...
リアルでオフコラボでホラーゲームをした時のサムネです。
...did an off-collab of a horror game,
and that's the thumbnail from then.
ころねの手書きです。あはは。
It's hand-drawn by Ko-ne. Ahaha.
あー楽しいな、クイズなんて。あ、
Ah, this is fun! To think there'd be a quiz...
マリンありがとうクイズ考えてくれて！
Marine, thank you for coming up with the quiz!
嬉しい、なんかサムネイルとか遡ってくれたのかな。
I'm happy you went back and
looked at my thumbnails and stuff.
えー、なんかコメントもいっぱいありがと。ありがとね。
And thank you for all the comments!
Thank you so much!
スパチャもありがと！嬉しい。
Thank you for the Super Chats too! I'm so happy.
じゃあ次の問題いこうかな。
Well then, I think I'll move on to the next question.
じゃあ第3問、お願いします！
Now, question number three! Here we go!
スバルがころねに密かに憧れている点は？
What point of Korone does
Subaru secretly admire?
え、スバルちゃん？
Eh, Subaru-chan?
体力？スバルちゃんあるしな。
Physical strength? Subaru-chan has that too.
ゲーム愛？スバルちゃんあるしな。
Love for games? Subaru-chan has that too.
女子力もスバルちゃんあるしな。
Subaru-chan has feminine charms too.
えーむずい！これちょっといきなり難しくなった。
Man, this is hard! This got hard all of a sudden.
え、何だろう。これ何だと思う、みんな。
What could it be? What do you think, everyone?
全部？えっ。
Everything? Eh.
あ、密かにか。そう、密かだ。
Ah, 'secretly', huh? Right, 'secretly'.
今、運営さんからヒントが降ってきました。「密かですからね」って言われた。
I just got a hint from the staff. They said,
"It's 'secretly', you know."
じゃあファッションセンスかな？
Then, is it Fashion Sense?
え、待って。ちょっと待って。何だろう、ファッションセンス？
Wait, wait a second. What could it be?
Fashion Sense?
これ間違えたらライブできない？
If I get this wrong, I can't continue the live show?
だめ？だめか。
No? Is it no?
いや、なんかやだな、自分がオシャレですって言ってるみたいでやだけど...
It feels weird to say I'm stylish myself, but...
...でも、たぶんファッションセンスかな。
...it's probably Fashion Sense.
ファッションセンス！
Fashion Sense!
いいんですかって聞いて、なに？センスないって言いたいんですか？
You're asking if it's okay? What?
Are you saying I have no sense?
ファッションセンス！
Fashion Sense!
えっ。
Eh?
あぁー！なんで落とすの！なんで間違えて落とすの？
Aaaah! Why did you drop me?
Why drop me for getting it wrong?
聞いてたんだけど、落とされたんだけど！
I was listening, but I was dropped!
落とされた、ひどい！
I was dropped! How mean!
女子力？
Feminine charms?
え、なんかこれコメントもらってるんですか？
Oh, did I get comments about this?
あ、コメントもらってます。密かに。
Ah, I am getting comments. 'Secretly'...
ひどい、落とされたよ、みんな。
Mean! I was dropped, everyone.
え、スバルちゃんそうなの？密かにころね女子力？
Wait, is that so, Subaru-chan?
Secretly admiring Korone's feminine charms?
へぇー。なんかあれだね。
Heh. That's, you know...
本当に密かだね。
It really is 'secretly'.
あ、ころね、あの...
Ah, Ko-ne... and...
なんかね、スバルちゃんのコメントで、「気遣いの鬼」って言ってたそうです。
Apparently, Subaru-chan's comment said
I'm "a master of consideration."
スバルちゃんありがとー！
Subaru-chan, thank you!
ありがとね、スバルちゃん。
Thank you, Subaru-chan.
え、じゃあ次の問題いこうかな。
Well then, I think I'll move on to the next question.
次の問題...
Next question...
カモン！
Come on!
あ、みおしゃだ、みおしゃ。
Ah, it's Mio-sha, Mio-sha.
え、ちょっと待って。なげーよ！
Wait a sec, this is long!
2019年7月25日に行われた、昔だな、ミオさんところねさんのコラボ...
In the collab between Mio-san and Ko-ne
on July 25th, 2019... that was a long time ago...
「どうぶつタワーバトル」で...
"Animal Tower Battle"...
20個以上積み上げる熱戦がありました。
...there was a heated match where
we stacked over 20 animals.
最後にころねが積み上げた動物で崩れてしまいます。
At the end, the animal Korone stacked
caused it to crumble.
さて、最後に積み上げた動物は何だったでしょうか？
So, what was the last animal stacked?
わかるかボケ！みおしゃはこれわかってるからクイズ出したんだよな。
How am I supposed to know, you dummy!
Mio-sha must know, that's why she made the quiz.
え、何だったっけ、これ。
What was it again?
たぶんね、シロクマじゃなかった気がする。シロクマはなし。
I feel like it wasn't the Polar Bear.
No Polar Bear.
え、何だったっけ。
What was it?
しまう、しまう... なんかね、線が細かったの、なんか。たぶん。
Zebra... I think it had thin lines. Maybe.
たぶん記憶的に、線が細かった気がする。
In my memory, I feel like the lines were thin.
シマウマ...
Zebra...
チーター、シマウマ...
Cheetah? Zebra?
シマウマ、あ、
Zebra... ah...
じゃあシマウマでいきます。
I'll go with Zebra.
いいよね、みんな。シマウマだよね。
Right, everyone? It's Zebra, isn't it?
シマウマ！
Zebra!
えっ。
Eh?
ちょっと待って、なんで落とす、なんでこう間違えて落とすん？
Wait a second, why drop me?
Why drop me for a wrong answer?
ひどい、落とされるよ、毎回。
How mean! I get dropped every time.
え、チーター？チーターだったっけ？
Eh, Cheetah? Was it Cheetah?
これね、でもよく覚えてる。あのミオしゃがね、いて...
Wait, I remember this well. Mio-sha was there, and...
...あの、オンラインで対戦したんだけど...
...we were playing online, and...
ミオしゃにこうやってぺんってビンタしたらミオしゃが「痛い！」っていう回だった気がする。
...I think it was the episode where I 'slapped'
Mio-sha and she said "Ouch!"
気になる方はたぶんアーカイブあるのでよかったら遡ってみてみてください。よろしくね。
If you're interested, the archive is probably still there,
so please go check it out! Please do.
たぶんその回だった気がする。
I think it was that episode.
あ、みよしさんありがとうございます！ありがとねみよしさん、ありがと！
Ah, Miyoshi-san, thank you very much! Thank you, Miyoshi-san, thank you!
じゃ、次の問題行こうかな。
Well then, shall we move on to the next question?
え、いいですか運営さん？早すぎる？
Eh, is it okay, staff? Am I going too fast?
全然正解してないですねって言われた。うるせえ！
They said, "You haven't gotten any right at all." Shut up!
じゃ、次の問題カモン！
Well then, next question, come on!
ラミィちゃんだ。とある相談中、『もしかしたら、ころね先輩に迷惑がかかっちゃうかもしれない…』という発言に対して答えたイケメンすぎる返答は以下のうちどれ？
It's Lamy-chan. In a certain consultation, which of the following was the too-cool response I gave to the statement, "Maybe I'll cause trouble for Korone-senpai..."?
①お前にかけられる迷惑ならご褒美だ
1. If it's trouble caused by you, it's a reward.
③うるせえ口を塞いでやるぜ（ちゅっ）
3. I'll shut that noisy mouth of yours (mwah).
②それで友達一人守れるなら本望だ
2. If I can protect one friend that way, it's what I want.
④とりあえず朝までゲームしよ
4. Anyway, let's play games until morning.
え、ちょっと待って恥ずかしいよラミィちゃん。ちょっと、ラミィちゃん恥ずかしいよちょっと。
Wait, hang on, this is embarrassing, Lamy-chan. Seriously, Lamy-chan, this is embarrassing.
これまで覚えて...
You even remembered this...
ちょっと待って、今なんか『再現して』って言われた.地獄なんですけど。
Wait a minute, I was just told to "reenact it." That's hellish.
それで友達一人守れるなら、本望だ。
If I can protect one friend that way, it's my heart's desire.
え？
Eh?
もう、こういう空気になるじゃん、絶対！イェーイじゃないんだよ。
See, it was definitely gonna turn into this kind of atmosphere! Don't "Yay" me.
じゃこれ、２番！あ、違う、２番２番！
Then this one, number 2! Ah, wait, number 2, number 2!
『それで友達一人守れるなら』ってやつ、お願いします！
The "If I can protect one friend" one, please!
当たりだねこれ。あ、よしよしよし！イェーイ！
That's correct. Ah, alright, alright, alright! Yay!
やめてよ、ちょっと撮らないで、ちょっとやめて。撮らないで、やめて。
Stop it, don't film me, stop. Don't film me, stop.
寄らないで、寄らないでよ。
Don't zoom in, don't zoom in.
ラミィちゃんありがとう。あの、その悩みの時はさ、あの、頼ってくれて嬉しかった、本当に。
Thank you, Lamy-chan. Um, when you had those worries, I was really happy that you relied on me.
ありがとうねラミィちゃん。あの、コラボも仕様ね、また。
Thank you, Lamy-chan. Let's collab again too.
ありがとうねラミィちゃん。恥ずかしいなちょっと、やだ。
Thank you, Lamy-chan. This is embarrassing, I hate it.
なんでその言葉かけたか、って言われた今。なんでかけたか。
I was just asked why I said those words. Why I said them.
え、でもラミィちゃんが好きで、あの、ラミィちゃんに気を使ってほしくなかったから、
Well, it's because I like Lamy-chan, and I didn't want her to have to be overly cautious around me,
あの、もっといいんだよっていう意味を込めてね、その言葉を言いました。
so I said those words with the meaning that it's okay to be more open.
なんで落とすん？なんで落とすんだよ！
Why are you dropping me? Why are you dropping me?!
ちょっと遊ばれてる気がするちょっと.戻るの大変なんだから、これ。
I feel like I'm being played with. It's hard to get back up, you know.
ちょっと意味もなく落とすのやめてください。
Please stop dropping me for no reason.
はい、じゃ、次の問題。まだある？まだあるかな。ある。じゃ、次の問題カモン！
Okay, next question. Is there more? I wonder if there's more. There is. Then, next question, come on!
えっと、こおねの家にお泊まりしたときにころねらしいなああと感動した瞬間はどれでしょう！
Um, which was the moment when staying at Ko-one's house that made me think, "That's so Korone," and feel moved?
①目が覚めたら配信していた瞬間
1. The moment she woke up and I was streaming.
②目覚まし時計が妖怪ウォッチだった瞬間
2. The moment the alarm clock was Yo-kai Watch.
③一緒のお布団では寝てくれなかった瞬間
3. The moment she wouldn't sleep in the same futon as me.
④ブラウザが大量に開かれていた瞬間（いらすとやがめちゃあった）
4. The moment the browser was opened in massive quantities (there was so much Irasutoya).
え、待って、どれ？え、とりあえず１はないんだよね、１はない。
Eh, wait, which one? Well, for starters, it's not 1, not 1.
目が覚めたら配信した瞬間はない。
There wasn't a moment where I was streaming when she woke up.
妖怪ウォッチだったのも多分なくって、え、４かな。４かな。
The Yo-kai Watch thing probably wasn't it either, so maybe 4? Maybe 4?
みんなが４て言うから４にしてみよう。これ！４番のブラウザが大量に開かれていた瞬間！
Everyone is saying 4, so let's go with 4. This one! Number 4, the moment the browser was opened in massive quantities!
なんで落とすの、しかも。え、全部バツってどういうこと？じゃ今の問題は？
And why are you dropping me, too. Eh, what do you mean they're all wrong? Then what about that question?
もう一回出して.え、今の問題全部当たりだったってこと？
Show it again. Eh, does that mean all of them were correct?
全部当てはまって.なんなのそれ、みこみこ！ちょっとおかしいよそれ.え、今のじゃ、ころねはさ、間違いになるってこと？
They all apply. What's up with that, Mikomiko! That's a bit weird. Eh, so does that mean for that one, I'm wrong?
ちょっとグルだ、これ運営さんとみこみこ.グルになっとる！間違いにカウントされるらしいです。
It's a conspiracy, staff and Mikomiko. They're in cahoots! Apparently it's counted as a mistake.
ちょっと待って、おねだりしてみよう可愛く。
Wait a minute, let me try begging cutely.
運営さん、当たりにしてください。
Management-san, please make it a 'correct' answer.
だめみたいだね。なんか、やっぱ可愛こぶるのは良くないみたいだ。
I guess not. Seems like acting cute isn't a good idea after all.
じゃ、次の問題。次の問題は、カモン！
Okay, next question. Next question is, come on!
ふぁ！これはフカヒレママだ、フカヒレママ。え、ころねちゃんの誕生日ケーキのかぶりものに載っている
Pwah! This is Fukahire-mama, Fukahire-mama. Eh, on Korone-chan's birthday cake headpiece,
ブルーベリーの数は何個でしょうか？（見える範囲で）
how many blueberries are there? (Within the visible range)
ころねちゃんの誕生日ケーキのかぶりものに載っているブルーベリーの数は何個でしょうか？(見える範囲で)
How many blueberries are on Korone-chan's birthday cake headpiece? (within visible range)
数の...
The number...
ブルーベリーの数？
Number of blueberries?
ブルーベリーの数...
Number of blueberries...
ブルーベリー...
Blueberries...
え、みんなわかる？
Eh, do you guys know?
ね、わかる？ね、ママからクイズ来た！と思って...
Hey, do you know? A quiz came from Mama! I thought...
...喜んだのもつかの間、ブルーベリーの数？
...I was happy for a moment, but then "Number of blueberries"?
何個？
How many?
7個？7個、選択肢ないだろって。
Seven? There's no "seven" option.
え、12個？それか10個かな？
Eh, 12? Or maybe 10?
いや、10...
No, 10...
10個か12個だな、きっと。
It's either 10 or 12, for sure.
19個もなかった気がする。
I don't think there were as many as 19.
ないよね、みんなね。ないよね。
Right, guys? Right?
10... いや、10！
10... no, 10!
そんなない、そんなないよ。
Not that many, not that many.
そんなない！
Not that many!
ということで、15！
So, 15!
あ、間違え... あ、あ...
Ah, wrong... ah, ah...
え、ここ？あ、え、10、10！
Eh, here? Ah, eh, 10, 10!
10！
10!
えー！
Eh—!
あー！
Ah—!
12だって。
It was 12.
え、12だったんだ、ママ。
Eh, it was 12, Mama.
ママ、ごめんなさい！
Mama, I'm sorry!
12だったんだって、みんな、12、12。
It was 12, everyone, 12, 12.
あらよー、12個かー。
Goodness, 12 pieces...
え、ちょっと待って、次で最後？
Eh, wait a minute, is the next one the last?
次で最後か？
Is the next one the last?
最後なのかな、次で。
Will it be the last one, next?
最後なのかな。え、じゃあ最後の問題、呼ぶよ。
I wonder if it's the last. Okay, then I'll call for the last question.
せーの、最後の問題こい！
Ready, set, last question, come on!
ころさーん、お誕生日おめでとう！
Koro-san, happy birthday!
おかゆー！
Okayu—!
ヤッホー。
Yahoo.
どこ？どこ？え、おかゆどこ？
Where? Where? Eh, where's Okayu?
今日はリモートだよ。
I'm remote today.
なんでだよー。
Why!?
絶対、絶対嘘だ、絶対。
Definitely, definitely a lie, definitely.
今日はリモートだよ。
I'm remote today.
え、リモート... え、じゃ、立ち絵とさ...
Eh, remote... eh, so, just a standee...
おかゆ。
Okayu.
わー！おかゆ嬉しいなー。
Wow! Okayu, I'm so happy.
え、おかゆ大きいね、ちょっと。あ、こっちもだ。
Eh, Okayu, you're big. Oh, over here too.
おかゆ、ありがとう、来てくれて。
Okayu, thank you for coming.
ころさーん、お誕生日おめでとう。
Koro-san, happy birthday.
嬉しい、ありがとう、ありがとう、ありがとう。
I'm happy, thank you, thank you, thank you.
え、なんで、なんで来てくれたの？
Eh, why, why did you come?
嬉しいよ。
I'm so happy.
もっと喜びを身体で体現して。
Express your joy more with your body.
嬉しい！
I'm happy!
足りない、足りない。
Not enough, not enough.
嬉しい！嬉しい！嬉しい！嬉しい！
I'm happy! I'm happy! I'm happy! I'm happy!
まあまあ、まあまあだね。
Well, it's so-so.
まあまあか... ちょっともっと勉強しとこ。
So-so... I'll study a bit more.
え、なんで来てくれたの？
Eh, why did you come?
いや、今日はころさんの誕生日だし...
Well, today is Koro-san's birthday, and...
うん。
Yeah.
やっぱ僕からもクイズ出さないとなーと思って来たんじゃ。
I thought I should give you a quiz too, so I came.
あ、クイズ持ってきてくれたの？
Ah, you brought a quiz?
もっちもち。
Of course.
え、どうしよう。えい、えい。
Eh, what should I do? Ei, ei.
クイズ聞きたい？
Do you want to hear the quiz?
え、もうちょっとイチャイチャしたい。
Eh, I want to flirt a bit more.
さあ、最後は僕から問題を出すよ。
Now, I'll give you the last question.
馬鹿野郎、はい、こい。
You idiot, okay, bring it.
こちら。
Here it is.
ころさんはご飯のとき必ず言う言葉があります！何でしょう！
Korone-san always says a certain phrase when eating! What is it?
ころさんはご飯のとき必ず言う言葉があります。何でしょう。
Korone-san always says a certain phrase when eating. What is it?
1. さあみんなで頂きますもしよ。
1. Now, let's all say "itadakimasu-moshiyo".
2. 腹減っただ、腹減っただ。
2. I'm hungry! I'm hungry!
違うわ、これ3だ、2。
No, that's 3. 2...
はー、いいニオイ、はー。
2. Haa, it smells so good, haa.
3. 腹減っただ、腹減っただ。
3. I'm hungry! I'm hungry!
4. ウェットティッシュ使う？
4. Do you want a wet wipe?
さあ、どれだ。
Now, which one is it?
え、全然わかんないんだけど。
Eh, I have no idea at all.
嘘つけよ。
Liar.
全然わかんないんだけど。
I have no idea at all.
もう、そっち行ってんじゃねーよ。
Come on, don't go over there.
え、えー、でもどれかな。え、みんなどれだと思う？ちょっと。
Eh, eh—, but which one? Eh, guys, which one do you think? A bit...
えー、どれ。
Eh—, which one.
みんなはちなみに、4かな、4、4、4... と言ってます。
By the way, everyone's saying 4, 4, 4...
4で出てる？
They're saying 4?
4、4、4... まあたまに2とか3とかもあるけど、まあ多かったのは4。
4, 4, 4... Well, there's the occasional 2 or 3, but mostly it's 4.
腹減っただ、腹減っただって言わんだろ、普通。
I wouldn't normally say "I'm hungry! I'm hungry!".
え、でも言いそう。とりあえず全部言ってみてよ。
Eh, but you might. Anyway, try saying all of them.
はいよ。
Okay.
さあ1。さあみんなで頂きますもしよ！
1. Now, let's all say "itadakimasu-moshiyo"!
お、言いそう。
Oh, you might say that.
はい2。腹減っただ、腹減っただ。
Okay, 2. I'm hungry! I'm hungry!
それ、それは3、それは3！2！
That's— That's 3! That's 3! 2!
同じ間違えしちゃった。
I made the same mistake.
それは3なんだよ。
That's 3.
はい、2。はー、いいニオイ、はー。
Okay, 2. Haa, it smells so good, haa.
おー、言いそうじゃん。
Oh, you might say that.
はい3。腹減っただ、腹減っただ。
Okay, 3. I'm hungry! I'm hungry!
言いそう、言いそうだね。
You might say that, yeah.
はい4。ウェットティッシュ使う？
Okay, 4. Do you want a wet wipe?
なんか、やっぱ4が一番言わなそうな感じするけどね。
Somehow, 4 feels like the least likely thing you'd say.
ね、なんかどうなんだろうね。4なのかな。
Yeah, I wonder. Is it 4?
今見た感じだと、まあ3とか2多かったけどね。
From what I've seen, there were a lot of 3s and 2s.
じゃあ, 4かな、やっぱり。
Then, maybe it is 4 after all.
自分のことは自分が一番わかってるからね。
Since you know yourself best.
はい、じゃあ、4でファイナルアンサーお願いします、おかゆさん。
Okay, then, 4 as my final answer, please, Okayu-san.
いいですね。じゃあ、正解は、4番、
Good. Then, the correct answer is option 4,
ウェットティッシュ使う？
"Do you want a wet wipe?"
ころねさんはご飯のとき必ず言う言葉があります！何でしょう？
①さあみんなで頂きましょう！ ②はー いいニオイ はー
③腹減っただ！腹減っただ！ ④ウェットティッシュ使う？
There's something Korone always says when eating! What is it?
1. Let's all eat together! 2. Ahh, smells so good, ahh...
3. I'm hungry! I'm hungry! 4. Want a wet wipe?
おかゆー！さっきからさ、聞いてよちょっと！
Okayu! Hear me out for a second!
なに、なに？
What is it?
さっきから正解して落とされるんだけど、どういうことなの？
I keep getting the answers right but then getting dropped. What's going on?
いや、遊ばれてるね。遊ばれてるよ、本当に。
You're being played with. Truly.
あ、ね、おかゆの立ち絵がなくなったんだよ。まだいるよ。
Ah, Okayu's avatar disappeared! She's still here, though.
あ、じゃあ僕の立ち絵が消えたということでね、今日は...
Well, since my avatar is gone, today I'll...
あ、ちょっと待ってよ、待って、まだ、まだ喋るよ、ちょっと待って喋るよ！
Wait, wait! I'm still talking! Wait, let me talk!
まだ喋る、まだ喋る。
I'm still talking! I'm still talking!
え、なんか、他にもなんかさ、言うことない？なんか。
Don't you have anything else to say? Like anything at all?
他に？
Anything else?
え、なんか、あの、今までほら、なんか、あんま最近さ、最近っても、二日三日喋ってないじゃんか。
Like, we haven't talked much recently. Well, it's only been two or three days, but still.
なんか、なんか頂戴、なんかある？
Give me something. Do you have anything?
えー、何だろう、まあ...
Hmm, let's see...
じゃ、今日も犬だね。
Well, you're a dog today too.
今日も犬だね。今日も犬だね、今日も犬。
A dog today too? Yeah, a dog today too.
そう、僕は今日も猫だよ。
That's right. And I'm a cat today too.
あ、そうなの。
I see.
え？ころさんにさ、今日、誕生日プレゼント持ってきたんだよ！
What? Actually, Koro-san, I brought a birthday present for you today!
本当に？！
Really?!
そう。
Yes.
なんか、何だろう。
What could it be?
ころさんのさ、左側に紐があるでしょ？
Koro-san, there's a rope on your left side, isn't there?
ある。
There is.
え、これ？
Is it this one?
そう、これ。すごい、なんか何だろう、何だろうって思ったんだよね。え、いいの？引っ張って。
Yeah, that one. I was wondering what that was. Is it okay to pull it?
そう、いいよ、引っ張っていいよ。
Yeah, go ahead and pull it.
行くよ、おかゆ。
Here I go, Okayu!
うん。
Okay.
はい！
Here!
痛いのって気持ちいいでしょ？
Being in pain feels good, right?
僕からはドMのプレゼントだよ。
It's a "masochist present" from me.
痛っ！
Ow!
でも良くない？気持ちいいかも。
But isn't it nice? It might actually feel good.
そう、その感覚絶対忘れないでね。
Right. Never forget that feeling.
じゃ、僕は行くからね。
Well, I'm off then.
おかゆ待って、まだ、まだ喋ろうよ。
Wait, Okayu! Let's talk some more!
うん、もう無理だよ。
No, it's impossible now.
じゃあね、バイバイ！
See ya, bye-bye!
ええー！
Eeh?!
なんで落とすの、上から！おかゆありがとうね！
Why do you drop things on me?! Thank you, Okayu!
ありがとう。
Thank you.
ということで、え、これ、もう一回引いたら、もう一回引いたらあれかな？
Anyway, what if I pull this again? Will it happen again?
ね、首、首取れる、首取れる！
My neck! My neck's gonna come off!
首取れるってこれ、やばいよ！
My neck's gonna come off, this is bad!
え、引いたら引いた分だけ来る感じ？
Does it come down every time I pull it?
ひどい！あ、でも、おかゆのプレゼントって聞いたらなんかちょっと嬉しくなっちゃったかもしれない。
That's mean! But hearing it was a present from Okayu made me a little happy.
え、ということで、あれかな？もうクイズは全部終わっちゃったんだけど。
So, I guess that's it? The quiz is all over.
多分、え、何問、何問正解しましたか？マネちゃんは。
Probably. So, how many did I get right, Manager-chan?
何問かな？
How many?
三問ぐらい？
About three?
半分以下っていう今ちょっと運営さんの声が聞こえましたけど。
I just heard a staff member say "less than half".
え、みんなさ、ライブできないかも、ちょっと。
Everyone, I might not be able to do the live show.
ほとんど正解だった！
I almost had them all right!
え、どうしよう、え、めっちゃライブ結構頑張って練習してきたんだけどな。
What should I do? I've worked so hard practicing for the live...
ねーねーねー。
Hey, hey, hey.
練習してきたんだけど。
I've been practicing.
え、待って、運営さん、ちょっと。
Wait, staff members, hold on.
あ、待って、待って、待って！
Ah, wait, wait, wait!
あ、ま、違う、違う、ライブ、ライブさせてください！今日、本当に頑張っ...
No, that's not it! Please let me do the live! I've really worked hard...
おかゆ！
Okayu!
運営さん見て、ほら。
Look, staff members.
見て！
Look!
やってもいい、あ！
Can I do it? Ah!
音が遅いんよ、ちょっと！
The sound is a little delayed!
なんで落とすの、え、これ戻ってきたってことは...
Why are you dropping me? Wait, since I'm back, that means...
あ！
Ah!
やってもいい？
Can I do it?
あ、みんな、今ね、運営さんから、えーと、誕生日だから仕方ねーなということで、ライブの許可が出ました！
Everyone! The staff just said, "Since it's her birthday, it can't be helped," and gave me permission for the live!
うぉー！ありがとう！ありがとうね、ありがとう！
Whoo! Thank you! Thank you so much!
え、ということで、ちょっとねころねも、あの、ライブステージに移動になるんだけど、え、もうちょっと戯れたいな、みんなと。
So, I have to move to the live stage now, but I want to hang out with you all a bit longer.
ありがとうね、みんなコメントたくさん見えてるからね。始まる前もずっと見とったし、今もずっと見とるからね！
Thank you! I can see so many of your comments. I've been watching them since before the start, and I'm still watching them now!
ありがとう。
Thank you.
運営さんありがとうだって！
They said "Thank you, staff"!
いぇーい！ということで、じゃ、ころねはライブステージに移動になります。
Yay! So, Korone will now head over to the live stage.
えっとね、後で結構重大発表とかもあるので、
I'll have some big announcements later, too.
そのまま見ててくれたらとっても嬉しいです。
So I'd be very happy if you'd stay tuned.
ということで、えーと、ちょっとした映像も用意したので、
And since I've prepared a little video for you...
それを見て待っててください！
...please watch it while you wait!
じゃあ、また後でね！
See you again in a bit!
頑張ってくる！
I'll go give it my all!
ふふふ...
(Humming)
テレビ楽しい。
TV is fun.
あ～、楽しいな～、楽しいな～。
Ah, this is fun, this is fun.
おっ？おっ？わあ！
Oh? Oh? Wow!
カメラ！
A camera!
見っけ！
Found you!
見てる～？ころねだよ～。
Are you watching? It's Korone!
いたっ！
Ouch!
なに？
What?
痛い。
That hurts.
タライ。
A washbasin.
あ～怖い、怖いけど、
Ah, it's scary, it's scary, but
でもカメラで遊びたい、遊びたい...。
I still want to play with the camera, I want to play...
みんな見てる～？ころねだよ～。
Is everyone watching? It's Korone!
ホロライブゲーマーズの、いたっ！
From Hololive Gamers— Ouch!
なに？
What?
誰？
Who?
誰もいない。
No one is here.
誰もいないよ。
There's no one.
なんで？
Why?
一回、一回はけるよ。
I'm going to, I'm going to step away for a second.
いないよ、
I'm not here,
ころねはいないよ。
Korone isn't here.
いないからね。
I'm gone, okay?
ひょっこ、
Peek...
ひょっこ。
Peek.
ここなら大丈夫かな？
Maybe it's safe here?
やっほ～。
Yahoo!
いたっ！
Ouch!
なんで？
Why?
どうして？
How come?
なんでころねだけ狙うの？
Why are you only targeting me?
あ、この部屋にころねしかいないからってこと？
Oh, is it because I'm the only one in this room?
逃げよう、
I'm escaping,
もうこんなところ。
from this place.
あ、もう一回遊んじゃおうかな。
Ah, maybe I'll play one more time?
やっほ～。
Yahoo!
いたっ！
Ouch!
だめだ、
No!
ちょっとこんなところ、
I can't stay in a place like this,
もう嫌だ！
anymore!
痛い痛い痛い！
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
もう嫌だ！
I'm done!
わあ！
Whoa!
ここまで来ればもう大丈夫だね。
I should be safe if I've come this far.
ということで改めて、
So, let me try this again.
おはよー！
Good morning!
ホロライブゲーマーズの、
From Hololive Gamers,
戌神...
Inugami...
ちょっ、ちょっ、ちょっと待って！
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
いたっ！
Ouch!
痛い！
It hurts!
なんで、なんで私なの？
Why, why is it me?!
痛い！
Ouch!
ホロライブ、
Hololive...
おはよー、
Good morning...
ころね、
Korone...
あ～～！
AHHHH!
「ワイワイワールド」
作詞：河岸 亜季　作曲：菊池 俊輔
"Wai Wai World"
Lyrics: Aki Kawagishi / Music: Shunsuke Kikuchi
きたぞ きたぞ アラレちゃん
Here she comes, here she comes, Arare-chan!
キーン キンキン キンキン キン
Zoom, zoom zoom zoom zoom!
テケテケテッテッテー
Teke-teke-tettettee!
ピッピッピッ プーペッポ ガッちゃんも
Pip-pip-pi, poo-pep-po! Gatchan too!
夢の爆弾 うちあげろ
Launch a bomb of dreams!
お日さまニコニコ ぶたさんホホケキョ
The sun is smiling, the pig says "hohokekyo"!
みんな あつまれ ペンギン村に
Everyone gather in Penguin Village!
どんなことが おこるかな
I wonder what will happen?
それゆけ イッシッシ おたのしみ
Off we go, hee-hee-hee, it's going to be fun!
あそぼ あそぼ アラレちゃん
Let's play, let's play, Arare-chan!
ウッチャッチャッチャッ チャッチャッチャ
Utchatchatcha chatchatcha!
ツンツンツン ツンツンツン ガッちゃんも
Poke, poke, poke! Gatchan too!
おもしろ爆弾 うちあげろ
Launch a funny bomb!
お空はあおあお 博士はエッヘッヘ
The sky is blue, the Professor says "eh-heh-heh"!
みんな あつまれ 始業のベルだ
Everyone gather, there's the school bell!
いったい なにが はじまるか
I wonder what's about to begin?
それゆけ イッシッシ ドキドキわくわく
Off we go, hee-hee-hee, so exciting and thrilling!
わらっちゃお わらっちゃお アラレちゃん
Let's laugh, let's laugh, Arare-chan!
キャハハハハハ キャハハハハハ
Kyahahahahaha kyahahahahaha!
クププププーペッポ ガッちゃんも
Kupupupupoo peppo! Gatchan too!
笑いの爆弾 うちあげろ
Launch a bomb of laughter!
お月さまキラララ みんなもキャハハハ
The moon is sparkling, everyone says "kyahahaha"!
みんな あつまれ おまつりだ
Everyone gather, it's a festival!
うちゅうのはてまで とびいりさ
We'll fly all the way to the edge of space!
それゆけ イッシッシ おどらにゃそんそん
Off we go, hee-hee-hee, you're missing out if you don't dance!
みんな あつまれ おまつりだ
Everyone gather, it's a festival!
うちゅうのはてまで とびいりさ
We'll fly all the way to the edge of space!
それゆけ イッシッシ おどらにゃそんそん
Off we go, hee-hee-hee, you're missing out if you don't dance!
「Happy Halloween」
作詞・作曲：Junky
"Happy Halloween"
Lyrics & Music: Junky
Happy Halloween
作詞・作曲 Junky
Lyrics & Composition: Junky
日も暮れ 暗くなりそうだから
The sun is setting and it's getting dark,
出ちゃってもいいかしら
So is it okay if I come out?
ちょっとね 魔法にかけられた
Just a little, I've been put under a spell
キミのお菓子から食べちゃおう
By your sweets, so I'll start eating them!
きっと 霧が濃くなるから
The fog will surely get thicker,
みんな集まるかな
I wonder if everyone will gather?
じっと 甘いもの我慢した
I've been patiently resisting sweets
ご褒美は ほら 一つ二つ
My reward is, look, one or two...
鐘の音 さあ 小さいオバケたち
The sound of the bell—come now, little ghosts!
今日はお菓子をくれないなら
If you won't give me any candy today,
街の邪魔しに行こう
I'll go and play tricks on the town!
だって Happy Halloween
Because it's Happy Halloween
イタズラしちゃうぞ Ding-Dong-Dang
I'm going to play a trick on you, Ding-Dong-Dang!
あっちもこっちも トリック・オア・トリート
Trick or treat here, there, and everywhere!
キャンディはくれないの？
Won't you give me any candy?
だって Happy Halloween
Because it's Happy Halloween
大嫌いなカボチャもポッキー
Even the hated pumpkins and Pocky...
疲れたジャックも踊るよ
The tired Jack-o'-lantern will dance, too,
朝まで
Until the morning!
だって Happy Halloween
Because it's Happy Halloween
オバケの株だって上がっちゃう
Even the ghosts' stock is rising!
今日は 街中 トリック・オア・トリート
Today, the whole town is "Trick or Treat!"
チョコも頂戴よ
Give me some chocolate, too!
だって Happy Halloween
Because it's Happy Halloween
不思議な世界へようこそ
Welcome to a mysterious world
疲れたジャックも歌うよ
The tired Jack-o'-lantern will sing, too,
Let's Trick or Treat
紅い家なんて 庭先に
To a red house, or just in the yard,
トイレットペーパー ぐるぐるしちゃえ
Let's wrap it up in toilet paper!
今夜はランタン 灯してるなら
If you're lighting lanterns tonight,
甘いの頂戴 さあ
Then give me something sweet, come on!
Let's party night
ほら だって Happy Halloween
Look, because it's Happy Halloween,
時計も回るよ チクタク
The clock hands turn, tick-tock!
あっちもこっちも トリック・オア・トリート
Trick or treat here, there, and everywhere!
目もくらむ パンプキンパイ
A dazzling pumpkin pie!
だって Happy Halloween
Because it's Happy Halloween,
だから 夜更かししちゃうじゃない
That's why we're staying up late, isn't it?
疲れたジャックも寝ないわ
The tired Jack-o'-lantern won't sleep,
朝まで
Until the morning!
だって Happy Halloween
Because it's Happy Halloween
今日は Happy Halloween
Today is Happy Halloween!
さあ Let's Trick or Treat
Come on, Let's Trick or Treat!
赤いカボチャも 転がして
Roll the red pumpkins, too,
朝まで 寝たくない
I don't want to sleep until morning!
ハッピーシンセサイザ
作詞・作曲 BETTI
Happy Synthesizer
Lyrics & Composition: BETTI
ハッピーシンセサイザ
Happy Synthesizer
君の胸の奥まで
To the depths of your heart,
届くような メロディ 奏でるよ
I'll play a melody that reaches you
儚く散った 淡い片思い
A fleeting, faint unrequited love,
笑い話だね 今となれば
It's just a funny story now, looking back
見るもの全て 輝いて見えた
Everything I saw looked radiant,
あの日々は 綺麗に笑ってるよ
Those days are smiling beautifully
我慢することだけ 覚えなきゃいけないの？
Do I have to learn only how to endure?
「大人になって頂戴」言わなくていいよ
You don't have to say "Become an adult, please"
知らないことばかり 知らないなんて言えなくて
There were so many things I didn't know, and I couldn't say I didn't
大変
It's tough...
お似合いね、嘘ついてごめんね
Looks good on you, sorry for lying
ハッピーシンセサイザ
Happy synthesizer
君の胸の奥まで
Reaching deep into your heart
届くようなメロディ奏でるよ
A melody that reaches you, I'll play it
つまらない建前や
Boring pretenses
嫌なこと全部
And all the bad things
消してあげるから
I'll erase them for you
この音で
With this sound
何の取り柄もない
I have no special talents
僕にただ一つ
There's just one thing I can do
少しだけできること
Just a little bit
心踊らせる
Making your heart dance
飾らない言葉
With unadorned words
電子音で伝えるよ
I'll tell you with electronic sounds
好きになること理屈なんかじゃなくて
Falling in love isn't about logic
こじつけなんていらないんじゃない?
Explanations aren't needed, right?
時代のせいと諦めたらそこまで
If you blame the times and give up, that's where it ends
踏み出さなくちゃ何も始まらない
You've got to take a step or nothing will start
ごめんね、夜遅く寝てるところだったでしょう
Sorry it's so late, you were probably sleeping
驚いた私も駆け出そうとしてた
Surprised, I was also about to run off
心の裏側をくすぐられているような
Feels like the back of my heart is being tickled
響きあう二人に幸せな音を
A happy sound to the two of us resonating
ハッピーシンセサイザ ほら楽しくなるよ
Happy synthesizer, look, it's getting fun
涙拭くメロディ奏でるよ
A melody to wipe away tears, I'll play it
強がらなくたっていいんじゃない別に
You don't have to act tough, it's fine, really
自分に素直になればいい
If you just stay true to yourself, it'll be okay
何の取り柄もない僕にただ一つ
I have no special talents, there's just one thing
少しだけできること
I can do just a little bit
ちょっと照れるような単純な気持ち
A bit embarrassing, simple feelings
電子音で伝えるよ
I'll tell you with electronic sounds
ハッピーシンセサイザ 君の胸の奥まで
Happy synthesizer, deep into your heart
届くようなメロディ奏でるよ
A melody that reaches you, I'll play it
つまらない建前や嫌なこと全部
Boring pretenses and all the bad things
消してあげるからこの音で
I'll erase them for you with this sound
何の取り柄もない僕にただ一つ
I have no special talents, there's just one thing
少しだけできること
I can do just a little bit
心踊らせる飾らない言葉
Unadorned words that make your heart dance
電子音で伝えるよ
I'll tell you with electronic sounds
ハッピーシンセサイザ ほら楽しくなるよ
Happy synthesizer, look, it's getting fun
涙拭くメロディ奏でるよ
A melody to wipe away tears, I'll play it
強がらなくたっていいんじゃない別に
You don't have to act tough, it's fine, really
自分に素直になればいい
If you just stay true to yourself, it'll be okay
何の取り柄もない僕にただ一つ
I have no special talents, there's just one thing
少しだけできること
I can do just a little bit
ちょっと照れるような単純な気持ち
A bit embarrassing, simple feelings
電子音で伝えるよ
I'll tell you with electronic sounds
せーの
One, two...
でもそんなんじゃダメ
But that's no good
恋愛サーキュレーション
作詞 meg rock ・ 作曲 神前 暁
Ren'ai Circulation
Lyrics: meg rock / Composition: Satoru Kosaki
もうそんなんじゃほら
Look, that's enough already
心は進化するよ もっともっと
My heart is evolving, more and more
言葉にすれば消えちゃう関係なら
If it's a relationship that vanishes when worded
言葉を消せばいいやって思ってた
I thought I should just erase the words
恐れてた
I was afraid
だけどあれ?
But wait...
なんか違うかも
Something might be different
千里の道も一歩から
A journey of a thousand miles begins with one step
石のように固いそんな意志で
With a will as hard as a stone
塵も積もればやまとなでしこ?
If dust piles up, it becomes a Yamato Nadeshiko?
「し」抜きで、いや死ぬ気で!
Without the 'shi', no, with my life on the line!
ふわふわり ふわふわる
Fluffy, fluffy
あなたが名前を呼ぶ
Just you calling my name
それだけで宙に浮かぶ
Makes me float in the air
ふわふわる ふわふわり
Fluffy, fluffy
あなたが笑っている
Just you laughing
それだけで笑顔になる
Makes me smile too
神様ありがとう 運命のいたずらでも
Thank you God, even if it's a prank of fate
めぐり逢えたことが幸せなの
The fact that we met makes me happy
でもそんなんじゃダメ
But that's no good
もうそんなんじゃほら
Look, that's enough already
心は進化するよ もっともっと
My heart is evolving, more and more
そうそんなんじゃやだ
Yeah, I don't like that
ねぇそんなんじゃもっと
Hey, that's not enough
私のこと見ててね ずっとずっと
Keep looking at me, forever and ever
あのあなたほど あなたの中の 私の存在はまだまだ
But my presence in you is not yet as big
大きくないこともわかってるけれど
as yours is in me, I know that, but...
今この同じ瞬間共有してる時間
This time, this moment we're sharing right now...
ちりも積もればやまとなでしこ
If dust piles up, it becomes a Yamato Nadeshiko.
略してちりつもやまとなでしこ!
Shortened to 'Chiri-Tsumo Yamato Nadeshiko'!
クラクラリ クラクラリュ
Dizzy, dizzy...
あなたを見上げたら それだけで眩しすぎて
Just looking up at you is far too dazzling.
クラクラル クラクラリュ
Dizzy, dizzy...
あなたを想っている それだけでとけてしまう
Just thinking about you makes me melt.
神様ありがとう 運命のいたずらでも
Thank you, God, even if it's a prank of fate.
めぐり逢えたことが しあわせなの
I'm happy that we were able to meet.
恋いする 季節は 欲張りに サーキュレーション
Love in this season is a greedy circulation.
恋いする 気持ちは 欲張りに サーキュレーション
Feeling in love is a greedy circulation.
恋いする 瞳は 欲張りに サーキュレーション
Eyes in love are a greedy circulation.
恋いする 乙女は 欲張りに サーキュレーション
A maiden in love is a greedy circulation.
ふわふわり ふわふわる あなたが名前を呼ぶ
Fluffy, fluffy... just you calling my name
それだけで宙に浮く
makes me float in the air.
ふわふわる ふわふわり あなたが笑っている
Fluffy, fluffy... just you smiling
それだけで笑顔になる
makes me smile, too.
神様ありがとう 運命のいたずらでも
Thank you, God, even if it's a prank of fate.
めぐり逢えたことが しあわせなの
I'm happy that we were able to meet.
でも そんなんじゃ だめ
But that's not enough, see,
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
that's not enough...
心は進化するよ もっともっと
My heart will evolve, more and more.
そう そんなんじゃ いや
Yes, I don't like it like that,
ねえ そんなんじゃ まだ
hey, that's not enough yet...
私のこと見ててね ずっとずっと
Keep looking at me, forever and ever.
恋愛裁判 作詞・作曲：40mP
Love Trial / Lyrics & Composition: 40mP
Oh! No! No! No! ちょっと魔がさしたんだ
Oh! No! No! No! I just had a momentary lapse.
そう、僕は君だけが全てさ
Yes, you're everything to me.
ねえ、情状酌量をください
Hey, please give me some leniency.
僕一人じゃ生きていけない
I can't live all by myself.
Oh! Jesus! そんな目で見ないで
Oh! Jesus! Don't look at me with those eyes.
もう、金輪際心入れ替えるよ
I'll turn over a new leaf starting now, I swear.
だから、執行猶予で
So, let me off with a suspended sentence,
一度だけ見逃して
and overlook it just this once.
計画的な犯行の
Even my alibi for this planned crime...
このアリバイ工作も
I can't fool only you.
君だけは騙せない
With these cheap tricks, no, no, no!
小手先の手品じゃ No! No! No!
It's truly a love trial.
まさに恋愛裁判
How much of a crime will you charge me with?
君は僕にどれくらいの罪を問う？
After the tears of the final statement,
最終弁論の涙の後に
the verdict you gave me was 'Guilty'.
君から告げられた僕は「ギルティ」
Guilty!
Oh! No! No! No! 最悪の事態だ
Oh! No! No! No! This is the worst-case scenario.
そう、君にフラれるくらいなら
Yes, if I'm going to be dumped by you...
ねえ、いっそ君の手で僕を
Hey, I'd rather have you push me
暗闇に突き落としてよ
down into the darkness with your own hands.
Oh! Jesus! 論より証拠だ
Oh! Jesus! Proof is better than theory.
もう、僕は取り繕わないよ
I won't try to cover it up anymore.
ずっと、君の監獄に
You can even lock me up
閉じ込めてもいいから
in your prison forever.
性格的な問題と
Due to character issues
一度だけの過ちで
and just a one-time mistake,
君はもう戻らない
you won't come back anymore.
口先の弁護じゃ 許されない
I won't be forgiven by these lip-service defenses.
恋愛裁判
Love Trial
どこが完全犯罪？君も僕も同じだけの
Where is the perfect crime? You and I, both with the same...
悲しみを
...sadness.
愛した人　愛された人
The one who loved, the one who was loved
互いを裁き合う運命だから
It's our destiny to judge each other
有罪判決　君は僕にどれくらいの罪を問う？
Guilty verdict. How much of a crime will you charge me with?
終身刑で償う覚悟
Prepared to make amends with a life sentence
死ぬまで君だけを守るよ
I'll protect only you until I die
恋愛裁判　君が僕に教えてくれた真実
Love Trial. The truth that you taught me
偽りの涙の後で
After those false tears
密かに微笑んだ小悪魔
A little devil smiled secretly
君もギルティ
You're guilty too
極楽浄土
作詞：MARiA　作曲：toku
Gokuraku Jodo
Lyrics: MARiA  Composition: toku
月明かり昇る頃 灯る赤提灯
When the moonlight rises, the red paper lanterns are lit
祭囃子の合図 ふわり 蝶が誘い出す
The signal of the festival music, a butterfly softly invites you out
ちょいと覗いて見てごらん
Take a little peek and see
迷い込めば抜け出せない
Once you wander in, you can't get out
楽しいことがしたいなら
If you want to do something fun
おいでませ 極楽浄土
Come on over to the Sukhavati
歌えや歌え 心のままに
Sing and sing, just as your heart desires
アナタの声を聞かせて
Let me hear your voice
踊れや踊れ 時を忘れ
Dance and dance, forgetting about time
今宵共にああ狂い咲き
Tonight, together, ah, blooming madly
美しく咲く花も いつか散りゆくもの
Even the flowers that bloom beautifully will one day scatter
それならこの一夜を もっと熱く愛したい
In that case, I want to love this single night even more passionately
ちょいと「いいこと」いたしましょう
Let's do something "good"
これは夢か幻か
Is this a dream or an illusion?
嘘も真もない世界
A world with neither lies nor truth
ゆきましょう 極楽浄土
Let's go to the Sukhavati
歌えや歌え 心のままに
Sing and sing, just as your heart desires
乱れる髪を気にせず
Without worrying about your messy hair
踊れや踊れ 時を忘れ
Dance and dance, forgetting about time
今宵共にああ狂い咲き
Tonight, together, ah, blooming madly
ちょいと「いいこと」いたしましょう
Let's do something "good"
嘘も真もない世界
A world with neither lies nor truth
ゆきましょう 極楽浄土
Let's go to the Sukhavati
歌えや歌え 心のままに
Sing and sing, just as your heart desires
アナタの声を聞かせて
Let me hear your voice
踊れや踊れ 時を忘れ
Dance and dance, forgetting about time
今宵共にああ狂い咲き
Tonight, together, ah, blooming madly
今宵アナタと狂い咲き
Tonight, blooming madly with you
はい、極楽浄土でした。
Yes, that was Gokuraku Jodo.
どうだったかな？
How was it?
えーっと、次の曲が最後なんだけど、
Um, the next song is the last one,
少し準備があるので
but I have some preparations to do,
お知らせを見て待っててください！
so please watch the announcements and wait!
はーい！お知らせ担当のころねだよ！
Hi! It's Korone, in charge of the announcements!
最後の曲の前にお知らせだよ！
I have some announcements before the last song!
戌神ころね誕生記念グッズが出ます！
Inugami Korone Birthday commemorative goods are coming out!
グッズは全部で4種類！
There are four types of goods in total!
まずは、なもり先生描き下ろしの
First, the BIG Acrylic Stand
BIGアクリルスタンド！
illustrated by Namori-sensei!
制服もなもり先生に考えていただきました！
Namori-sensei also designed this uniform!
すごい可愛いです！
It's so cute!
続いて、細居先生描き下ろしの
Next, the Muffler Towel & Sticker Set
マフラータオル＆ステッカーセット！
illustrated by Hosoi-sensei!
闇ころねとボクシングしている様子のタオルです！
It's a towel showing a boxing match with Dark Korone!
ライブで使ってもいいし、野球観戦に使ってもいいので、
You can use it at lives or at baseball games,
よろしくお願いします！
so please check it out!
続いては、ころねとおそろっちマグカップ＆
Next is the Matching Mug Cup
獅子唐ティースプーンです！
and Shishito Tea Spoon!
これはころねも配信で使ってるからみんな知ってるね！
You all know this because I use it in my streams!
完全にころねとおそろっちなので、
Since it's exactly the same as mine,
持っていたら多分気分がいいと思います！
it'll probably make you feel great if you have it!
最後は、ころねすきーとピキピキピーマンのピンバッジ！
Finally, the Koronesuki and Pikipiki Piman Pin Badges!
これを付けてればみんなピキピキころねすきーだ！
Wearing these makes you a Pikipiki Koronesuki!
フルセットで購入してくれた暁には、
If you purchase the full set,
今回限定の特別サインが付いてるポストカードと、
you'll get a limited edition autographed postcard
ミニ「ありがとう」ボイスが付いてきます！
and a mini "Thank You" voice message!
グッズはこの後10時から発売開始です！
The goods go on sale today at 10:00 PM!
よろしくね！
Please check them out!
最後の曲の準備が整ってると思うので、
The preparations for the last song should be ready,
ライブ会場にお返しします！
so let's go back to the live venue!
みんなで呼んでみよう！
Let's all call out together!
せーの、ころさーん！
Ready... Korone-saaan!
じゃーん！
Ta-da!
これは何の衣装でしょう？
What outfit is this?
そう、オリ曲のドレスです！
That's right, it's the dress for my original song!
100万人記念で作ってもらっちゃいました！
I had it made for my 1 million subscriber celebration!
可愛いでしょ！
Isn't it cute!
このライブが終わってから、10時15分くらいからかな？
After this live, at around 10:15 PM maybe?
メンバー限定配信でこのドレスの撮影会があるから、
I'll have a photo shoot in this dress on a members-only stream,
よかったらそちらも見に来てね！
so please come watch that too if you'd like!
さっきお知らせにあったグッズはこの後10時から、
The goods from the announcement go on sale at 10 PM today,
発売開始ですのでよろしくね！
so please check them out!
ということで、この衣装を着ているということは...
And so, since I'm wearing this outfit...
何を歌うか分かるよね？
you know what I'm going to sing, right?
では、最後の曲、聴いてください！
Now, please listen to the last song!
ころねの最強天才ワンダフルワールド！
Korone's Strongest Genius Wonderful World!
おはーよー ころねすきー
Good morning, Koronesuki!
ユビユビ ユビ頂戴
Yubi-yubi, give me your fingers!
ななな なんでそんなに 他の子のこと詳しいの？
Why, why, why do you know so much about other girls?
あっそっか よその配信にも入り浸ってたね みんな
Oh, I see. You've all been hanging out in other streams.
いいんだよ ころねは全然気になんかしないからね
It's okay. Korone doesn't mind at all.
バカ！
Stupid!
パン屋さんの隅っこ配信
Streaming from the corner of a bakery,
チャンネルの掛け持ち配信
streaming across multiple channels.
ご褒美の圧 かけ開始 熱投 見ていてね
Starting to apply pressure as a reward. Watch my passionate throw!
おもち焼いて こげこげチョップ
Baking mochi, scorched chop.
爪破壊して ユビユビ脅迫
Breaking nails, yubi-yubi threat.
浮気したリスナー共 ずっとバレないって思ってるでしょ
You listeners who cheated, you think I won't find out, right?
小指のその先へ モニター越しの仲
Beyond the pinky finger, friends through the monitor.
赤い糸 結び 千切れ 千切れ 千切れ
The red thread of fate—tie it, tear it, tear it, tear it!
そろそろ始まるよ 時刻は 激アツ
It's about to start! The time is super hot!
さあ みんな準備は OK?
Now, is everyone ready?
HEY! GUYS! ARE YOU READY?
YUBI YUBI
IT'S SHOWTIME!
奇跡的 刺激的
Miraculous, stimulating,
ワンダフル 最強天才 パーリナイ
wonderful strongest genius party night!
空気読んだら 小石ほど 素晴らしい 呼吸
If you read the room, it's as wonderful as a pebble's breath.
みんなとの お約束
The promise with everyone,
圧力 愛情 全開 ハピタイ
pressure, love at full throttle—happy time!
宇宙規模の 大絶叫 ポケポケ
Universe-sized scream, poke-poke,
ギュギュっと ハート掴んじゃうよ
squeeze, I'll grab your heart!
ぴったり156メートルの身長
Standing at exactly 156 meters tall
キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエル
A Cavalier King Charles Spaniel
笑顔と体力が自慢です
I'm proud of my smile and stamina
好きになっていいんだよ
It's okay to fall in love with me
長時間の配信
Long-hour streams
クリア目指し邁進
Pushing forward to beat the game
みんなの指、ボッシュート！食べたい 食べたい 食べたい！
Everyone's fingers, confiscated! I wanna eat 'em, eat 'em, eat 'em!
膝の皿で乾杯 酌み交わした仲
Cheers with kneecaps, friends who drink together
ほらみんなもうおともだち！
Look, we're all friends now!
今日きて奇、今日きて奇
Insane today, coming today
ぶっころね神聖パーティ・カーニバル
Bukkorone's holy party carnival
立ちはだかる敵キャラ射抜いたオーケー
Snipe the enemies blocking the way, okay!
みんなにもおすそわけ
Sharing it with everyone
戯れ爆ぜてハピネス
Playing around, bursting with happiness
まだ終わらせない絶対
I won't let it end, absolutely
ずっとずっと想ってるから
Because I'm thinking of you forever and ever
大丈夫、無理しないでね
It's okay, don't push yourself
いつも付き合ってくれてありがとう
Thank you for always being with me
すごく感謝してるんだけど
I'm really grateful, but...
他の女のとこ行かない？
You're not going to other girls' streams, right?
許さないかんね！今日も見てんよ よろしくね！
I won't allow it! Watching you today, take care of me!
Are you ready?
ヨイヨイヨイ！
Yoi yoi yoi!
ほていとー！
Po-te-to!
さあようこそおいでませ
Now, welcome, please come in
ワンダフル奇想天外ワンダーランド
A wonderful, bizarre wonderland
みんなとなら一緒に楽しめるよ
With all of you, we can have fun together
今日きて奇、今日は素敵
Insane today, today is lovely
ワンダフル舞い踊れカーニバル
A wonderful, dancing carnival
放送犬も忘れないでいざ大暴れ
Don't forget the broadcasting dog, let's go wild
奇跡的、刺激的
Miraculous, stimulating
ワンダフル最強天才フェスティバル
A wonderful, strongest genius festival
宇宙一の大熱狂
The universe's greatest excitement
今日はずっとハート離さないよ！
I won't let go of your heart today!
ワン・ツー・サン・ハイ！
One, two, three, go!
ころねのハッピーエンド！
Korone's happy end!